Morioka Hachiman style, guess how to read it?
Great!
I'm taking pictures of this high up right now.
Oh!
Yes!
All right! Thank you for the food!
Thank you for the food!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
It was really good!
We are too full
I'm too full, so I'd like to have a little after-dinner service.
The staff is now serving the soba noodles that you just made.
We were just saying the name of the place near the restaurant, right?
This is your first time taking a walk, isn't it?
Guess how to read Morioka Hachimangu Shrine.
Aaah!
I'm going to the Ryouke Hachiman Shrine here now, too. Look how beautiful it is...
I can see why it's so nice that there's no staff here, it really makes you feel like you're on vacation. I'm already wearing this dress I got earlier.
I'm not going to wear it all the time.
I've never been to this kind of place before, so it's more like a way of thinking, you know, like putting your pet in your mouth.
I don't know how to do it, so I want to, but I can't
I want to do it, but I can't...
I'm sorry, it's just so nice, I love it like this.
It's not too cold, it's not too hot, it's just right.
It's just perfect.
It's beautiful.
We're at the sparkling place.
I want to take a picture.
What's that?
It's a windmill.
Wow!
This is so cool!
It's so dreamy!
A windmill that carries your thoughts
May the wind carry your thoughts
May the wind carry your thoughts to God
I wonder if I should make a wish
I wonder if I should go in with them
Beautiful
Did you make a wish? Did you make a wish? I made a wish.
Beautiful.
Come here for a minute.
Oh, it's beautiful.
Beautiful, isn't it?
I'm taking a picture with this angle of view.
It's dazzling.
Oh, what's this?
That's amazing.
I've never seen anything like this before.
And it's so good!
Amazing!
Oh, look.
Oh!
It's a fortune!
Wet fortune!
Hey, I'm home.
You don't have anything on you?
I do.
You have? Oh, my God.
I don't have any money.
Can I go change some money? There.
Do you have it?
Yes, I have it.
Do you want me to?
Exchange money.
Money exchange.
Exchange time.
But, do you think you can understand this?
Oh, no.
I'm only allowed to put in 1,000 yen.
I don't know what to do.
Down, down, down, down!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What can I do?
I've got money...
I really want to pull it off.
It's too close for now.
I'll go back.
I'll go back one more time.
How's it going? Satiety settling down?
I'm fine.
I don't know. It's nice, isn't it?
The wind is blowing.
Blowin' in the wind
Sway, sway, sway
I'm going to be free
It's a song about you and me, isn't it?
It's great!
I want to go to a place like this since I'm going all the way across the country... like Ettusa... and the view from here... is really nice.
This is nice.
It's like a trip... emo-emo-emotional...
It's emo... emo... emo... emo... emo...
Oh my God!
I'm telling you, there's a lot of bus tours!
cticamente nobody
It's so dark!
I'll go!
I want to have fun!
I want to win the drinking lottery.
Let's do it!
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Hey...
It's a cut condition.
Cut. Cut. Cut.
Cut back.
That's right.
Okay.
Then we'll go again.
Yes, sir.
We're going to see the timey-two-shoes timings now!
I wonder what we'll get...
What's going to happen?
We want to get out...
The best one is "Daikichi
Daikichi, kichi, chukichi...
Shokichi?
Good luck is pretty high up.
Daikichi, kichi.
Daikichi, kichi, chukichi
Daikichi. Good luck.
Chukichi.
I don't know where the "suekichi" comes in.
Shokichi
Kyo, Dai-kyo
That's a tough one.
It's not that I want this to appear or anything.
Yes, yes...
It's important that you can do what it says.
That's important.
Really.
I see.
We'll both have little kids.
When the little ones come...
This staircase is the best we can do.
I know, right?
It's so long.
Right?
Even an adult would think it's long.
But even if you call yourself an adult...
Rocco, you're still a kid.
Yeah, but... you're an adult.
That's what a kid would say.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Six?
You're 16.
Sixteen?
We're all 17 this year.
Seventeen is a kid.
No, no, no.
I was barely 18.
Hey...
You have to hold a knife even if you don't want to.
I can't go against that.
I won't stop.
You did your best.
Yes, I did.
Now it's time for the mail timing.
I'll be back.
Yes, sir.
If we hit it, it's a huge Mediterranean exchange.
I'm curious.
Oh, my God...
Please use the provided fishing rod for your Mediterranean fortune.
Sorry, I only have 14 yen.
Oh, this is it?
What?
No problem.
I'm sorry.
Then, pull the tools from Momi. Or rather, fish with them.
Okay, I'll do it.
I want gold.
Gold? Here you go.
Gold.
It's big.
Yay!
Rocco, you sure did once.
Close your eyes, it's so good!
Okay, here we go.
You got it? Not quite.
This is good. I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it!
Oh! Red!
I caught it!
Okay, I'll open the package.
I'm going to draw a fortune now.
Ta-da! Sei-no, japan!
It's a medium lucky one!
I'm so lucky!
Wait a minute, let's read it.
Wait a minute.
Stay humble as much as possible, and don't do anything on your own initiative.
In other words, don't do anything by yourself.
Don't go on.
You should humble yourself as much as possible and not do anything on your own initiative.
So it's better not to do anything.
Well, I think it's a good thing.
I think it's a good thing.
If you try to force things, you'll get into trouble.
So it's better not to do it.
I see. I see.
I've had many heartbreaking experiences with my relatives.
I've been so troubled and pained that I've left everything to the heavens until the end of time.
I'll leave everything to the heavens until the end of time, and if I keep quiet and keep myself in check, I'll be as happy as the snow disappears in the morning sun.
It's so good!
You're kidding? Is it? What's this?
Because, you know, you just let it happen. You just let it happen.
What? Is that what you're saying?
I mean, it's important to do your best.
But it's like this guy says.
If you wrap yourself up quietly, you'll have a good time like snow disappears in the morning sun.
Isn't that great?
Yay!
I don't know... but I think it's good.
Study... make up your mind early.
Study with peace of mind.
Which is it?
Does that mean it's good?
You mean it's good?
It's fine.
No, I think it's good.
Oh, good, pull back.
I'll take care of it.
I'll take this home with me.
I'll bring it back.
Good night.
Which way do you like it?
But I knew it would be this way.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
It's good.
It's so cute!
Yay!
Mega mouse!
Makes me cry.
thanks for watching!
doh!
That's amazing!
It feels so real.
Yeah, it is.
Okay, let's split it.
Okay.
I'll put some soup in it.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you. - Yeah.
Thank you. Thank you.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Yup. - Yup.
Yes, I'm hungry. Lovely. I want to add quite a bit of spiciness.
I think it's good.
All right.
Well then, after a full day of sightseeing in Iwate today, I really love Iwate Prefecture again. Once again. I love Iwate. Even cuter.
Confession, confession. Please confess to Iwate Prefecture. Remember.
Please confess to Iwate Prefecture.
Iwate, I love you. I love you.
Accepted?
Well, well, well.
Can I show you how it's done?
Why not?
I can give you some guidance, but it's one-sided.
Come on.
I love you more than I love the soba noodles I've grown to love today.
Thank you.
Why are you impressed? It's great.
Why? Bon appétit.
Bon appétit. I'm tired now.
Bon appétit. Looks delicious.
It looks good. Mochi Mochi.
It's so elastic!
Bon appétit!
It's delicious, isn't it?
Yeah, it tastes different than usual.
I thought, they didn't put vinegar in it.
You put vinegar in this?
You put a lot of vinegar.
Why?
Because I usually put a lot of vinegar.
Oh, that's what you mean?
Yeah, that's what I mean.
What is it? Does it taste authentic? It tastes so authentic. It's like it's the real thing.
It doesn't mix.
It's so elastic, I can't even chew it.
Is it spicy?
You could add more.
It's so sticky!
Cucumber is delicious!
It's surprisingly easy to make!
It tastes better with vinegar!
It makes it more sour!
It's so refreshing...
Delicious!
The noodles remind me of wanko soba.
Mayu telegram streak
C volteMac is like a guitar flow in a cocoon!
Sorry if I take a lot!
It's really good!
Delicious?
It's very hot!
It's very easy to eat.
You know what I mean? Can you tell?
I've had so much delicious food today.
I've had so much delicious food today that I have more than enough power right now.
So I have no choice but to explode at the concert tomorrow.
If I can, I'd like to try the three best noodles I couldn't eat...
Jaja-men.
I wish I could eat it.
I'll do my best tomorrow.
I think that's good.
YES!
CLEAR!
Momo Kitahara and
Tsutsui Rocco.
You know, we also made a goal of 60 cups for Wancos.
We set a goal of 60 cups, and we've achieved it!
We're going to get a reward!
Yay!
I'm so excited!
What?
Yay!
Yeah!
I'm so happy!
You know what I mean.
I've always wanted to eat there.
I could have had cold noodles and one cosmo.
I wanted it.
What?
Thank you.
What was that?
What kind of crackers?
Can I open it now?
It's like a jumble.
You messed up?
It's cute.
Cute?
It's a key chain.
But if you look, there are different kinds.
Oh, yeah?
Christmas! Matching keychains!
I mean, there's squid crackers, apple crackers...
But the best one, the standard one, the Nambo rice cracker.
I won!
There are so many varieties!
So many varieties, but I'm sure this one
They match!
Yes!
Thank you!
I'm going to have to try this one.
Nambo senbei (soft rice cracker)
Thank you so much! I'm so happy!
I'll do my best! I'm just starting now.
I'll do my best!
Thank you for watching!